Kostadis Roussos: Are you fucking kidding me?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello. Hello. Can you hear me?
Nikhil: Yes, I can hear you. Can you hear me?
Kostadis Roussos: Of course they can, yes, of course.
Kostadis Roussos: Same? Right. Roll 20. You must be hot.
Nikhil: super hot and uh i'll tell you something else uh the central ac controls
Kostadis Roussos: Are with the house owner. Oh no.
Nikhil: I set the temperature and locked up that box so I don't even have the you know ability to control the temperature and each room has a fan so I just turned on my fan it's still hot
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, that's like cruel. Is he allowed to do that? I guess he is.
Nikhil: So, a lot of the, you know, house owners who rent out houses like this, they do that in San Jose and, you know, the Bay Area.
Kostadis Roussos: Really?
Nikhil: Yeah, I guess a couple of my friends' houses like before COVID.
Kostadis Roussos: uh seven years ago yeah they were renting that's really sucks yeah i know so i have a space heater in my room
Nikhil: For winters because I cannot stand cold at all.
Kostadis Roussos: God.
Nikhil: It's really hot. It gets really cold in the winters and I don't have the temperature control.
Kostadis Roussos: So I have a little speech.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let's see. Okay. So, do you remember what happened last time? Feel free to say. Okay. No, no, I'll tell you. Let me tell you, then we can explain.
Nikhil: So we went to that cave, manor, and we found a...
Kostadis Roussos: Secret route and there was a cave
Nikhil: And we went inside the crypt, there was a beast
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly.
Nikhil: Playing like mind games like you can control your mind and stuff
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I just want to remember what it said last so I don't forget.
Nikhil: I'm glad I remembered. My memory is working.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, that's very impressive. Yes, that is true. All right. So, let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. So yes, so you entered here and saw that the creature, the creature, what does the creature do? The creature speaks, reveals, revealed something about Pip. And what did he reveal? Let me see the recording. He revealed, let's see if I can pull this up, he revealed that
Kostadis Roussos: All right, I need to bring up my editor.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, he reveals that his, uh, he revealed that
Kostadis Roussos: Pip had recently won a strange blackstone shard in a dice game near Neverwinter Night Darks, then sold it to a peddler heading out toward Phandelin. Since then, Pip has dreamed of a broken blackstone beneath the earth, and heard whispers saying his name.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip wants to find the peddler, buy or steal the shard back, and figure out why it is haunting him.
Nikhil: Talking out loud, all of this.
Kostadis Roussos: Um, I think it's a mind, I think it speaks, I think it's a mind creature. So it's only talking to it, or? No, no, it's talking to all of you.
Nikhil: Can all of us hear this?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes, yes, all of you can hear it, but the only person who can understand it is Sister Mela, since none of you speak Undercommon. She quickly translates.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, the creature then explains, I am hungry, and offers to let you go if you're just willing to sacrifice one of your own.
Nikhil: That's why we have this Redbrand.
Kostadis Roussos: You're like, okay, you're gonna like, uh, toss him to the wolves? No, no, I'm gonna, um...
Nikhil: I mean I'll try to negotiate with the creature like
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so we'll give you one of...
Nikhil: One of us, as we will sacrifice one of us but want to be continued.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna, um, Zenvon is gonna talk to the creature, like, or maybe...
Nikhil: Tell Sister Meila to convey this thing, like, translate this to the future.
Kostadis Roussos: Alain, just give me a second. All right, so you're going to try to convince, you're going to have Sister Mele, so the creature looks at you and goes, looks at you and it kind of licks its lips.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, as it licks its lips, you realize that it's got fangs that are going out of style.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Just a couple of...
Nikhil: So is the creature loose or is it chained to something?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, roll an Investigation check. Roll for everyone. Would you roll?
Nikhil: Maia, yeah, 16.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Thanks for having us on RD20.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you notice a dead goblin, but it's kind of interesting. These goblins have elongated skulls and are dressed in filthy haphazard rags. Alright. Alright.
Nikhil: I'm going to ask...
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I can't hear you. Hold on. No, it's not you. It's on me. All right, speak.
Nikhil: Can you hear me?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I can't, I can't, I can't.
Nikhil: okay so uh i'm gonna um um talk to the red brand and ask like uh what is this creature why is it and a bit along the way.
Kostadis Roussos: What? Why does it have the, the, the, the, the, um, oh, you're talking to them. He's going, I'm not talking to you. You're gonna, like, give me, feed me to that creature.
Nikhil: No, Ted, you know, we need to know, like, if you tell us how to get past the situation, we'll be saved.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I don't know how to get past the situation. I told you man, somebody came down here and came down to this lower area and never came back. And there was like rumors about why he never came back.
Nikhil: Is this one of your guys? The guy who's dead?
Kostadis Roussos: No, he says, he looks at it and goes, I've never seen any goblin that looks like that.
Nikhil: And is the creature chained? So this question is to you. So is the creature chained or is it like roaming freely there?
Kostadis Roussos: With the creature with the claw, the teeth.
Nikhil: Yes, the Minecraft
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, he's kind of trying to figure out what you guys are going to do.
Nikhil: Is it chained or not?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, he's not changed. He's not changed, okay. He is absolutely not changed. Okay.
Nikhil: So yeah, like I said, I'm going to try to negotiate with the creature that will sacrifice one of us and...
Kostadis Roussos: Thanks for watching!
Nikhil: What are we going to get in return?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. He goes, um, I'll only eat one of you. Sure, but what?
Nikhil: Can we do?
Kostadis Roussos: You can continue to explore this area, and I don't have to tell you, and I won't kill you.
Nikhil: How do we trust you?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I like living, and why would I kill you if I've been fed?
Nikhil: It seems like a nice creature. Cool, uh, okay then, uh, we'll sacrifice the Redbrand.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, the Redbrand? Is that your plan? So you're going to turn on him? All right. Hold on. Give me a second now. Hold on. Okay, you're going to sacrifice the Redbrand. Okay, the Redbrand...
Kostadis Roussos: What does the Redbrand do? What does the Redbrand do? Okay, so first of all, the Redbrand does not just sort of like take it, like, he doesn't take it...
Kostadis Roussos: What's the word I'm looking for? Okay, if you want to hear... Okay, here's the audio. I put the link into the audio. If you want to hear creepy audio.
Nikhil: Yes, opening.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the creature, okay, so, I mean, your intuition is the creature isn't going to, um, freely negotiate.
Nikhil: What do you mean by that?
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, when I said freely negotiate, I misspoke. What your goal is, yeah, okay, so you want to give, you're going to give up Rondar, right? Okay, when Rondar hears that, he decides to bolt and starts screaming.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching.
Kostadis Roussos: This way.
Nikhil: I can't hear the sound.
Kostadis Roussos: Uh, you can't? If you click on that link...
Nikhil: I did, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: and you make sure you've turned on your audio volume for it you don't have it
Nikhil: I do, yes, I mean, volume is on because I can hear you, speaker.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I mean make sure that the vault, it's going through a, make sure you've got the web page, uh, doesn't, it's not muted accidentally.
Nikhil: It's not. Sound is automatic and default. Reset the corner.
Kostadis Roussos: Could you share your screen with that webpage on?
Nikhil: You see, uh...
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, show, show, show me the audio, that, that, the, the audio's coming, it's just not popping, it's not going to your, click start, yeah, there's audio coming because that's what you can tell from over here.
Nikhil: Let me switch my monitor.
Kostadis Roussos: or
Nikhil: browser because it's hold on let me try it on a different browser Syrinscape is not supported in Safari and I'm going to switch to a different monitor
Kostadis Roussos: Okay!
Kostadis Roussos: You don't see the boxes in my room because I moved the table. Dude, I'm not a fool. I know you hid them. That's okay.
Nikhil: No, no, the boxes are still there.
Kostadis Roussos: Hi, I know you hid them from me. You were very careful to make sure that I would not lecture you about the boxes again.
Nikhil: I changed my room orientation. I moved the table to the window side and bed to the center.
Kostadis Roussos: We need more things. Bye-bye. That's right.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Tell me when you're ready.
Nikhil: I'm ready but I cannot hear this
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Cannot hear it? It's okay. It's definitely playing on your computer. The only other thing I would say is you may be disabled. Anyway, let's deal with it some other time, shall we?
Nikhil: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I might be able to do it differently.
Kostadis Roussos: You may be able, maybe you hear it now through my speaker.
Nikhil: Thank you very much.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Let's see. Did you hear? Let me just say this.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You heard that? Yes. Okay, cool.
Nikhil: Thank you for taking the time.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. I'm sharing my computer audio. That'll work. All right. Okay. So the Nothic speaks to you again. Okay. So, okay.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Shit.
Nikhil: Thanks for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: And so Rondar decides he's had enough. He's going to run. Roll for initiative.
Nikhil: Gonna run.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, dude, you just said I'm gonna feed him to the Nothic, and he's not gonna sit there. He screams help, and he runs. But, you know, your master quiet plan did not quite work. Meanwhile, Pip's kinda like, dude, you're a cold bastard.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let's roll for initiative.
Nikhil: Yes, once again.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Ok. Mm-hmm. That's ok. So, um, 10. Ok.
Nikhil: Okay, my initial tools are...
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so 3D20. Let me just roll for initiative for the three, the three, los tres, los tres amigos. All right, so Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, move all turns, there, alright, so Pip, turn, is a 16, alright, who's next, Sister Mela, turn is a 10, Zerabira is a 19,
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra, where is she, Veyra, Veyra is over here, and then Sister Mela, turn is 10, what was yours? What's yours? Fifteen. Sorry, thirty.
Nikhil: 13, 1-3
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 13. And, uh, Rondar. 7. Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Pip, you're up first. Okay, Pip's up. What does Pip do? What does Pip do? So this creature's clearly going to come after you. He started shouting. He's decided that the... But!
Kostadis Roussos: the good news is that anybody who's out here probably thinks that the person is about who's screaming help is screaming help because of the monster not that he's actually trying to be saved right and so from your perspective so pip does pip realizes that and says
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder what to do next. So Pip will try to knock Rondar prone.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Shub, that's what I'm looking for. No, that's not it. Okay. So, I'm knocking someone prone. Shub? Oh, I had Shub.
Kostadis Roussos: Show of action! Alright, hold on, I need to figure out how to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, so he's going to try to knock him prone.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 8 plus your strength, okay so that's 15, 13, alright. Alright, so you're going to try to knock him prone. What does he do? His strength is plus 2, his proficiency is 12, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not too bad. All right. So, okay. Tries to knock him prone so he doesn't run away. Okay, so I guess he's going to do a dexterity. All right. All right. That did not succeed. Okay. Zenvon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip steps over here. Alright. Zenvon, you're up. You can see the map, right?
Nikhil: Yes, I can see. I'm going to move.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Uh, do the...
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, you can either sap first or nick first.
Nikhil: I know, I know, I'll do the neck so that I can, you know, hit and move back.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. That is a miss. All right, that was a natural one. All right, next tech.
Kostadis Roussos: But you get an advantage on your second attack. No, you don't. You get roll again.
Nikhil: Same scimitar or should I?
Kostadis Roussos: The other, the other weapon. Short sword or dagger, I don't know which one, what it is. Alright, roll for, click on the roll damages.
Kostadis Roussos: 12 points of damage all right he's down to four no he's down to he's down to four hit points down to four hit points not eight down he's down four all right
Nikhil: Okay, I'm going to move back.
Kostadis Roussos: all right um okay we're gonna move back
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay. Sister Mela looks at Rondar and says, what does she say? What does Mela do?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Sister Mela decides that, you know, this guy is a crook, a criminal, a thief, and a scoundrel. And, you know, quite frankly, he's not a good person. And as far as she's concerned, that means that, you know, she's done with him. And she goes, it's nothing personal, you see, nothing personal.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, you can't expect me to not think it's personal when you're about to kill me. She goes, yeah, I could see how you could see it that way, but I don't. So she strikes with her dagger. Went up with her mace, hits, and kills him. All right. The Nothic says, what does he say?
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic is pleased. He is very pleased.
Nikhil: Is it going to grant us any wishes?
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Does it come back forward because it's a pain?
Kostadis Roussos: What did you say?
Nikhil: Is it going to grant us any wishes because it's a mind creature?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's not. It's going to grant you the right to not die. He comes over here, and he drags the body over there.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, so are you guys going to just try to fight him or are you going to move on?
Nikhil: Find the creature?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I'm like, yes, I mean, he's eating, he's gone, he's taken Rondar. He's now dead.
Nikhil: Thank you!
Kostadis Roussos: Pip turns to you Zenvon and says, where do we go next?
Nikhil: So, we try to enter the manor.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you're in the manor, right? You're in the basement of the manor, right? Yes, so we try to get into the hall of the manor.
Nikhil: Closing this part like we need to get there and
Kostadis Roussos: You know, shut the door for the night, let's go.
Nikhil: I think that's it. That's the plan.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, you're currently in the Redbrands hideout to go, like, defeat the Redbrands and see who the boss is, right? That's, if you recall, that was, so you're trying to find out who's the boss. And so there's a passageway to the east and a passageway to the west. Which way would you like to go?
Nikhil: East is this one, on to my left
Kostadis Roussos: We, always we. East, that is left to your left would be west.
Nikhil: Okay, you said V, that's an acronym. Okay, left is west.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil: East is right. Well, I mean, we can definitely ask the Nothic.
Kostadis Roussos: No, the Nothic's not interested in talking to you. I mean, Sister Meela says, Zenvon, we probably want to get there before he decides he wants to eat more.
Nikhil: Okay, so I would want to go to the west.
Kostadis Roussos: The West? All right.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, um, uh, okay, okay.
Nikhil: How about this guy, the dead goblin?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you notice he's got an elongated skull.
Nikhil: Correct, yes, yes, is there anything else?
Kostadis Roussos: And no treasure.
Nikhil: Only three characters, like Veyra is missing.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Veyra is missing?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she was over here. She's here.
Nikhil: Okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay. So Zenon, let me just get the, let me just get this. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. You see a doorway over here. What would you like to do? Do you want to listen at the door? Or how do you want to take that?
Kostadis Roussos: Listen at the door. All right, roll your perception. What's your passive perception?
Nikhil: Perception is plus two.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 12. If you see on your character sheet, there should be a 12 and there should be a passive perception. Alright, you hear various creatures in the door.
Nikhil: Wait, what? Do I hear creatures?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, on the other side of the door. Roll your investigation or insight to see whether you can figure out what kind of creatures.
Nikhil: So it is plus zero, that is the investigation plus four, that is where we are going to be investigating. Fifteen.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 16. All right. You hear there's several bugbears in that room. They're talking and they seem to be laughing. You also hear the sound of a goblin.
Nikhil: Okay, I see two doors on the map. One is behind me, one is in the front.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's where you, so to the south is where you heard the creatures. Okay. Let me just write this here.
Nikhil: Can I go to the other door next door?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you can, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely.
Nikhil: Yeah, okay, I'm gonna go on to the other side of the door and do the perception and investigation, same practice again. So, do I need to roll an investigation?
Kostadis Roussos: let me see a roll of perception yeah oh your passive perception is a 12 all right roll an investigation all right
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie. You hear, whereas in the other room there were bugbears, this one you can hear what are clearly humans laughing and playing some kind of gambling game.
Nikhil: So bugbears, in my opinion, seem to be more dangerous than the humans, so I'll try to go on to the north side, north shore.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, um, okay, so you're going to open the door? Now, let somebody else, so Sister Mela, Pip, Veyra says, so what's the plan, boss? Just as you're about to open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Mail, uh, Pip says, Boss, you know that other door? They might come out from that other door. How do you, what are we going to do if we're kind of trapped between the two groups?
Nikhil: Just to make sure both the doors locked.
Kostadis Roussos: No, not really. They're closed. They're not locked.
Nikhil: I can just barge into any one of them, right? So, okay, so here's the plan, Veyra.
Kostadis Roussos: Weeble
Nikhil: All four of us, I kick the door open and we all get in and close the door behind us and see what the humans are doing and always be prepared to attack and try to, you know, we have the element of surprise so
Nikhil: try to we are four of us and try to get to four humans and you know
Kostadis Roussos: Put the sword to the neck.
Nikhil: Thank you very much.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're trying to try to surprise them, right?
Nikhil: Price Attack
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on. All right, so, okay. So, all right, so you're going to try to burst into the room and try to surprise them. Okay, roll your stealth, I guess. Yes. All right, everybody roll your stealth. Okay. That was not very good stealth, buddy.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, but I might
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: That might have been enough given these guys passive reception. Yep, you met you all of you man it you managed to surprise the group Okay, the door opens you see these four bandits let me just describe read to you what you see
Nikhil: Oh, just four of them. Four of them. Okay, cool. We'll get one of them.
Kostadis Roussos: Several worn tables and chairs are scattered around this large room. Wooden benches are drawn up against the walls, decorated with brown and red draperies, and several ale kegs are propped up and tapped. Four tough-looking human warriors wearing scarlet cloaks are gathered around one of the tables. A stack of coins and trinkets is heaped upon the table between them.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you've decided you're going to go for the kill?
Nikhil: Eh?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
Nikhil: I mean, not for the kill. Like I described, I want to hold each one of them as a prisoner and then talk to them.
Kostadis Roussos: Before Dishonored
Nikhil: Does that work or are they too strong for me to do that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, um, uh, Pip says, uh, boss, there's like four fighters there and two of us and...
Nikhil: Okay, okay, I'll change the plan. So we'll fight them and then we'll get them to their knees, down to their knees and then maybe talk before we can.
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra says, I think that plan works best if you coordinate it with the sign, with like, and she starts going off on her crazy talk again.
Nikhil: Yeah, yeah. You picked the strongest one, Veyra.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Oh, she's very happy. She's like, oh, thank you. All right. Okay, Zenvon, what's your initiative?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. And, uh, Pip. Alright. So, um, uh, right. What did you get for initiative?
Kostadis Roussos: Eight. That's it. Eight. 17. Maela is four. Yes, that's right. Is two. End. Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra is 8. Alright, Pip goes first, so Pip charges in and whacks, attempts to, no, so that's Mele. Pip charges in and...
Kostadis Roussos: bandits sort of look at him he looks at them and it says never did like the crooked kind it never did like the crooked kind and he rolls to hit
Nikhil: It was a heroic entry.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Pip definitely did the heroic entry. He's got to say, what does he get to a hit? Plus four to hit. I think that's enough to hit this guy. Yes, it is. Alright, so he takes, um, how much does he take?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, it takes six points of damage. All righty.
Nikhil: Quip attacks with one of them.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he attacks this one here. Can you see his, you should be able to see his.
Nikhil: The guy with the beard or the redbrand?
Kostadis Roussos: You should now see him.
Nikhil: Bandit
Kostadis Roussos: And you should now see him with less hit points.
Nikhil: Oh wow, I love this bar. This is really good.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay
Nikhil: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Veyra comes over here, and we'll cast Magic Missile. You could have done better, Veyra. All right, this Redbrand here.
Kostadis Roussos: Takes two points of damage. Alright, Xenophon, you're up.
Nikhil: I'll use my wicks.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, you just roll and then on the second attack you get advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: Uh, you did 12 points of damage? Against whom? Uh, no, you missed.
Nikhil: Wait, no.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 10.
Nikhil: I rolled a 10. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Now you get advantage on your second attack. Who do you want to attack?
Nikhil: Redbrand Ruffian
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? Okay. Go for it.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that one's a hit. Alright, damage?
Nikhil: Damages 11
Kostadis Roussos: oh he's down it the bandit is down to uh three hit points okay sister mela uh what does she do
Nikhil: I'm gonna be back
Kostadis Roussos: Thanks for watching!
Nikhil: Let's create a space for them.
Kostadis Roussos: If you move back, you're going to create an attack of opportunity. She doesn't need you to move back. She can walk around you. Alright. Alright, she's going to whack this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: And she kills him. Alrighty.
Nikhil: Can they attack even if they have like one hit point left?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they can attack. You're magically healed until your last breath. Alright, Pip. Okay, so it's Pip's turn, and Pip is going to attack the remaining...
Nikhil: Veyra, Veyra, Distant Oxide
Kostadis Roussos: Well, she's over here so she can cast spells. She doesn't have to be in the room.
Nikhil: Okay, but her turn did not appear yet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, she did. She cast Magic Missile.
Nikhil: Magic concern? Okay, no problem.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, all right, Pip. All right, so Pip will attack the Redbrand Muffin. How you gonna do?
Nikhil: In the back, or?
Kostadis Roussos: another one right in front and he will miss spectacularly all right okay that's Redbrand Ruffian all right
Kostadis Roussos: comes rushing at Sister Mela and shouts really loudly um okay uh screaming for the other bugbears to come help her and uh rolls to attack Sister Mela and misses
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the other Redbrand Muffian, thwacks, I don't know, thwacks at Xenophon.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Nine points of damage. No damage. He misses you entirely. All right. Veyra steps forward and casts a Firebolt. And misses. Zenvon, you're up. It's the luck of the draw.
Nikhil: I'll do the show vex again.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Nikhil: I did not miss this time.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, so you don't need your sneak attack, you can use your sneak attack on, well you can't because you used it, yeah, okay, this guy is dead. Alright, you can try to attack the other Redbrand.
Nikhil: I was thinking, can I attack the other Redbrand with this first attack and then second one with the dead guy?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, well, you don't know if you're going to hit the dead guy and you don't get advantage on the second attack because the vex only applies to somebody who hit.
Nikhil: I'm gonna wait for you, okay?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Roll again
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Ooh, hit! Right.
Nikhil: Each 12 points.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, only, uh, I guess, yeah, alright, so you did 4 points, you killed them with 4 points, you'll use a sneak attack here, you do 12 points of damage. Alright, okay.
Nikhil: I need the power of this thing.
Kostadis Roussos: oh yeah sorry all right okay what does the bandit do
Kostadis Roussos: Bandit comes this way and attacks Veyra because he wants to get through her to get out of here. And he hits her for four points of damage. All right, Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Mela, why don't you roll to attack for her to attack. D20 plus 4. She's going to hit with her mace. That is a miss. Alright. Well done. I just realized something. Pip has a special ability.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, hold on, sorry, he imposes a disadvantage on that attack, so maybe she doesn't take it. Oh, no, he would have still hit. Alright, so Pip will try to attack the bandit. Hits for six points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, the Redbrand Ruffian will thwack, I guess, Sister Mela and Mrs. All right, Veyra will use her second magic missile and hopefully do better this time.
Nikhil: So...
Kostadis Roussos: and kills them yeah she no she uses two on the bandit and one on the red brand they're all dead
Nikhil: That side, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: uh she was attacked she she you could definitely feel that she like this was a a sudden reaction now the one thing you do know is that there are bugbears coming by and the door is still open do you want to close the door do you want to barricade it in what would you like to do
Nikhil: I want to close the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, door is closed.
Nikhil: Yes, and then I was hoping to get some information out of the bandits and the Redbrands.
Kostadis Roussos: You might want to talk to Veyra about not killing all the bats.
Nikhil: Maybe, yeah, I'll explore the room to see if I can get any.
Kostadis Roussos: No, but if you don't want Veyra to kill people all the time, you probably need to talk to her and explain to her what you want.
Nikhil: Hey Veyra, I was hoping that, you know, we could have some information from one of these guys, but looks like you just killed all of them, right?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, they were about to kill me.
Nikhil: I get it. Like, you know, you can just, you know, damage them but not kill them, like, so that we can talk to them.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so I have to run to the bathroom. Nikhil, I'm going to run to the bathroom. I'll be back in two minutes. Give me a sec.
Kostadis Roussos: All right Where are we? Are you still there? Hey, uh, all right
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So Veyra is, you know, she's a... Rule your persuasion.
Nikhil: 11 plus the 30
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Veyra is partially convinced. Alright, you look at the treasure, so since you killed, since you managed to kill them all, you can seize their treasure, you find 75 copper pieces, okay, so let me just, let me just put this in the treasure, I'm going to put it in the zoom.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the discord chat, and then divide by four is going to be the simple rule, so, okay, so 75 copper pieces, 55 silver pieces, so that divided by four, so
Kostadis Roussos: We can deal with it later, alright?
Nikhil: I'll just put Flash 4, so yeah, go ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, um, alright, uh, while you're digging that, you, one of the, the door, the door on the other side opens, and a bug, you hear a bugbear knocking on the door.
Nikhil: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: and shouting in a very husky, bigberry, bushberry voice, Everything okay in there?
Nikhil: Yes, I'll roll my deception and try to respond in one of the Bandit or the Redbrand's voice.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: I don't know how their voice sounds but I will try
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you can, I mean, you can, I mean, who knows?
Nikhil: I'll try to make it up. I'll try to be a bandit and say it's all good.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay.
Nikhil: Deception Yeah, nice deception, yes
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's a nice deception. The bugbear shrugs and walks away. You hear the door close behind him. All right.
Nikhil: So, we'll explore the room. So, investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: You already did. There's nothing else here. The one thing you do notice is that the Redbrands have purple, have these red cloaks. You might want to take them to disguise yourself with them.
Nikhil: Okay, but there are only two cloaks, I suppose, like for the bandits, do they have cloaks as well?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they all, actually all of them, they all, they all have.
Nikhil: Cool. So I'll say to the team, guys, let's all pick up the cloaks and disguise ourselves.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I'll just put a little red dot to indicate that you're wearing the...
Nikhil: Redbrands.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, there's a door to the north.
Nikhil: yes i see that uh you guys want to go into that door or do you gonna go do you guys want to go fight the redbrands
Kostadis Roussos: What do you mean? What do you mean the Redbrand?
Nikhil: and other redbrands, the bugbears.
Kostadis Roussos: Um... Pip
Nikhil: Some of those per talk, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, we don't have to fight the bugbears, we could probably box them in by putting some of these barrels in front of the door.
Nikhil: That's really smart of you Pip. Okay, that's too bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you put some barrels in here, alright?
Nikhil: Take these barrels and park the tour.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Okay. Okay. I'll just draw something. A barrel has been placed in front of the door.
Nikhil: Peace.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright, I will assume you put more than one. Okay, so to the north door over here.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You're all dressed in your cool, snazzy, uh, outfits.
Nikhil: Yes, I want to again put my ear to the door and hear what's going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay?
Nikhil: Investigation
Kostadis Roussos: It is, there is, there is nothing there. There you hear nothing. Other than, let me see if I can do this again. Other than.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic is very happily digesting.
Nikhil: Well, that's the sound of them, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, should we open the door? Yes.
Nikhil: That's all for now.
Kostadis Roussos: all right the door is opened all right there's another door on the other side
Nikhil: So there's another door right after I open this door?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, yeah, there's a door right there. You can see it right in front. You can see that door, right?
Nikhil: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You're going to try to listen to that at that door as well.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, uh, what's your, roll your insight, or investigation.
Nikhil: I rolled the investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: and more events
Kostadis Roussos: You do not hear anything.
Nikhil: So it's a miss or do I not hear anything after?
Kostadis Roussos: Uh, uh, you do not hear anything. Um, Sister Mela says, have you tried cupping your hands? So she tries to help you. You can roll again.
Nikhil: 13
Kostadis Roussos: Still nothing.
Nikhil: What's to my east? Is it like the stairs?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it's the stairs, and through there you can definitely hear the Nothic.
Nikhil: Well, since we are disguised in cloaks, let's try to open the door and see what's happening. We are anyway like blended in them. What do you say guys?
Kostadis Roussos: They agree, so I'm assuming you opened the door. I was looking to play the appropriate sounds.
Nikhil: And I open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. This room appears to be a wizard's workshop. Alright, this appears to be a wizard's workshop. Hold on.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: A large work table is set up with alembics, retorts, distillation coils, and other alchemical devices, all of them stewing and bubbling away. Bookshelves are crowded with sheaves of parchment and strange-looking tomes.
Nikhil: Hey, Veyra, like, can you come over here? Looks like this is your playground.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh! What?
Nikhil: Looks like this is your playground. Why don't you come check this out?
Kostadis Roussos: she's like oh this is very cool um roll let's see what does she discover she rolls her arcana uh she goes well this is really interesting but i'm not sure i know what it's all about and she's like kind of like touches she's like you know that that person who goes into the jewelry shop and touches everything
Nikhil: Kid in a candy store
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Yes. Okay.
Nikhil: Did you find anything useful for Azvera? What are they trying to do here?
Kostadis Roussos: Period.
Nikhil: Open your feet.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Veyra looks at this and goes, oh, this is interesting, and says that this apparatus is set up to brew a potion of invisibility. Then she looks at the notes, but he hasn't been successful thus far. Sister Bela is perusing the books, and she notices one.
Kostadis Roussos: is written in Dwarvish. She picks it up. It's the journal of an adventure named Urmon. It describes the history of the Lost Mine of Phandelver and the Forge of the Spells.
Kostadis Roussos: In addition, Ormon records that a magic mate named Lightbringer was commissioned by the priests of Lathander, the gods of dawn, from the mages working with the gnomes and dwarves of the Phandelver Pact. The mace was lost when the Wave Echo caved, and its mine vanished from history.
Kostadis Roussos: There is a door to the north.
Nikhil: Can we pick up any of these potions or you know?
Kostadis Roussos: These equipment, um, uh, she, so, uh, Veyra looks at it and says, well, most of this room, most of the stuff here has no value, but these three bottles do, and she points out to three bottles with rare reagents, Mercury, Dragon Bile, and Powdered Nightshade.
Kostadis Roussos: Each worth 25 gold pieces each.
Nikhil: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay? Alright.
Nikhil: So now there's a door to the east.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: We'll open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, you can open the door. Hold on, hold on. All right. The walls of this bait chamber are covered with drapes of scarlet cloth. The furnishings include a small writing desk with a matching chair, a comfortable-looking bed, and a wooden chest at the foot of the bed. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You see a door to the north, which was clearly a secret door that somebody has clearly left. Alright. Okay, so do you want to go chase the guy who went through the secret door, or do you want to...
Kostadis Roussos: What do you want to do?
Nikhil: Oh, I wanna chase the guy through the secret door. Yeah. Hey guys, looks like somebody just left and opened the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Come on.
Nikhil: That's how we go.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right. All done.
Nikhil: Looks like it's leaving because I'm scared.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, yeah, I need to, give me a second, I need to do something, alright, so. Alright, okay, let's roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll?
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: That's strange. If now it is showing my name, then okay, that's from the beyond.
Kostadis Roussos: All right so we'll put I'll put pip in here uh that's 20 plus one this is plus two so that pip's a plus two that's 14
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela is just a raw d20, that's a 1, Veyra, Veyra over here, is a 16.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, she's got the time. No, she had a one. All right. Okay, so Veyra, one, two. Okay, Veyra goes one, two, three, four, five, six.
Kostadis Roussos: And, she sees, what's this guy doing? Let's make sure I have this correct. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: okay so he goes right okay Veyra sees him and says boss do I kill him or not
Nikhil: Wait, what's happening?
Kostadis Roussos: okay so stairs so you can she she she sees the bad guy she shouts to you do i kill him or not no you're it's not your turn yet
Nikhil: Oh, okay. Okay, I don't have a view of what's happening. No. Hold on. Don't hurt him, but don't kill him yet. Try to stop him from running.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she attacks him with her firebolt, and this time he does get hit.
Nikhil: No, those are the worst ones.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's see, alrighty, so she has a firebolt, 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: It would help if I put it in the right layer. Alright, okay, it takes five points of damage.
Nikhil: So, can I go by any stairs in Triboar?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, it's Pip's turn. You rolled very poorly on your initiative. So Pip goes 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. Pip uses his Javelin and hits.
Kostadis Roussos: Uh, what does he do? Uh, Javelin takes five more points of damage. Can you put the bar on this? Oh, yeah, sorry, sorry guys.
Nikhil: Baras Lelikovsko
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip, alright, so what does this guy do?
Nikhil: Space Yardland
Kostadis Roussos: You recognize him from the description Sildar gave you.
Nikhil: Thanks for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: All right, he like teleports himself. He's going to run this way, and then, all right, you have no idea what he's doing. Okay, shouldn't be able to see him. All right, Zenomon, you're up.
Nikhil: I'm gonna go up the stairs.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay, are we here? Yeah.
Nikhil: That may be a little bit tight.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Maybe I'll get it to the site, not of it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Um, I, okay, I'm gonna, before, one second, intimidation, yeah, I'll roll an intimidation, so I'm gonna ask him, do you wanna live or do you wanna die in our hands? Do you wanna talk or do you wanna fight first?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, um, he, he, you, you hear him, like, very far away, as if he's, like, run a hundred feet. The last thing you hear is him shouting to the Nothic, I pay you to protect this entrance, not to feast on whatever bodies I presented to you.
Nikhil: How about that? Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, what happened, okay, so just to tell you what happened. He ran 30 feet, then he cast Teleport.
Nikhil: and Teleport.
Kostadis Roussos: And he shouted to the Nothic to stop eating and to go fight whoever's chasing him.
Nikhil: So he's like 30 feet far from me.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's like 60 feet away. Do you have a short bow?
Nikhil: I have a short bow, yes, I'm gonna...
Kostadis Roussos: I was checking. Yeah, everything is like 5, I think.
Nikhil: and the U.S.D. Charter.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: What's the range of a shortbow?
Nikhil: ID
Kostadis Roussos: Is it 80 and 160?
Nikhil: 80 out of 320
Kostadis Roussos: Uh, you missed. Nice try. Alright, Sister Mela. What does she do?
Kostadis Roussos: what is sacred flame like she'll try to say what does she have let's have Sturmela she will try sacred flame all right
Kostadis Roussos: and he makes a saving throw all right he runs away the Nothic comes this way and says do you have any more food
Nikhil: Okay, so he escapes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he escapes.
Nikhil: Yes, yes, we have lots of food for you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: What do I do?
Nikhil: So just to understand from the secret passages going back into the...
Kostadis Roussos: The
Nikhil: Nothic's place, like where we entered from.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. I'm sorry. Yeah, basically what you've done is you started this way. Right? And foreground. You've gone.
Kostadis Roussos: It's your turn. Yeah, yeah. Pardon me. All right. All right.
Nikhil: Yeah, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget, you have the four other bodies in there and you can tell them to go eat them.
Nikhil: I know, that's why I said we have more food.
Kostadis Roussos: You tell them where they are?
Nikhil: Yes, we try to walk out of the same place and then we point them, we point the Nothic
Kostadis Roussos: The world.
Nikhil: The room where the dead bodies are.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic goes over here. Alright, what do you want to do next? Do you want to go look whether he left anything behind in his room?
Nikhil: Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I want to examine this table.
Kostadis Roussos: I thought we did actually. No, you examined his wizard's workshop.
Nikhil: Right, okay, so I want to go back and...
Kostadis Roussos: All right, uh, uh, Wizard Room. All right. I'm gonna go back, just go back, just place, okay, I'm doing it right here. All right, so what do we have in this Wizard's Room?
Nikhil: I'm disappointed.
Kostadis Roussos: or you just
Nikhil: Glasstaff
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right. The walls? Okay, so...
Kostadis Roussos: All right, various papers and notes are stacked on the desk, mostly consisting of Glasstaff's written orders to apothecaries and alchemists in nearby settlements for more materials for his workshop. However, you also notice a letter sealed with a wax symbol in the shape of a spider. All right, so I just showed you what the letter says.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you for watching!
Nikhil: Thanks for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Thanks for watching!
Nikhil: Thank you for watching.
Kostadis Roussos: Lost
Nikhil: Capture them if you can, kill them if you must, but don't allow them to upset our plans, see that any proven maps, their position will deliver to me with fear.
Kostadis Roussos: For more information, please visit our website at www.phandelver.com
Nikhil: Thanks for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Just to remind you, the spider was somebody you heard was the big boss of the goblins. Wait.
Nikhil: Spider was a character that I was introduced to.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I believe so.
Nikhil: oh yes yes uh a mysterious villain known as the spider controls the network of banded gangs
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. We can follow the Rockseekers to their prize. Right.
Nikhil: Thank you for your attention.
Kostadis Roussos: so so yeah so so the spider apparently so some somebody who maybe the spider or somebody who really likes uh uh spider art um sent him a note saying that you now have proof who Yarno really works for right which is which may be valuable to um uh to what's his name um Sildar Sildar
Nikhil: Find Gundren
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. You also know that Iarno was probably responsible for capturing Gundrun and Rockseeker. Yep. All right. Do you want to keep exploring?
Nikhil: Wait, I'm just gonna paste this letter from spider
Kostadis Roussos: It should, it should have, okay, yeah.
Nikhil: I'm just making notes, okay, what do I want to explore?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on. Okay, it just grabs the scrolls. All right, so inside, you do see an open chest where he was trying to, where there was a bunch of stuff there. It contains a bunch of gold. It contains a bunch of treasure.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, some more treasure.
Nikhil: What are Carnalians?
Kostadis Roussos: They're a kind of gem.
Nikhil: Okay, and Paragraphs are also...
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on. This is like, I don't know what they look like, so this is awesome. We can both find out. What was it? Peridots?
Nikhil: Very good, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: all right this is a peridot
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see that one. Carnelians. I mean, the thing I love about this is that, you know, this game requires you to be a gemstone expert.
Nikhil: They look like, vermilions look like red pebbles.
Kostadis Roussos: oh yeah copy image address and this is what uh this is what carnelians look like all right
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, um, there is a, there is a, there, you, you, all right, in this chamber where you are, you, you can, you hear the Nothic, uh, crunching his way through more cadavers. All right, let me just describe to you what this room here looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: This area is the north end of a large natural cavern, but it has been finished with dressed stone black walls and a flagstone floor. Several barrels are stored against the walls here, along with empty crates, straw for packing hammers, pry bars, and nails.
Kostadis Roussos: The cavern continues for some distance to the south. You can make out several passageways, then open off the larger cavern and what looks like a deep pit or crevasse in the floor.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, um, roll, uh, okay, so roll a insight or investigation.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll?
Kostadis Roussos: 14. You find a secret door.
Nikhil: Just to be clear, like, Glasstaff teleported or, like, you know, teleported himself or did he go through the secret door?
Kostadis Roussos: he went through the south let me just i'll just i'll draw tell you where he went actually he didn't go this way yeah he the last you saw him was he went that way
Nikhil: Okay, like all of the caves, from where we came, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. All right.
Nikhil: Open the secret door.
Kostadis Roussos: You're going to open the door? Alright, go in.
Nikhil: I don't see that at all.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a locked door. That's a locked door.
Nikhil: Both of them are locked.
Kostadis Roussos: uh no the door right right across from you is locked hold on let me just do something as you open the secret door
Nikhil: Should I keep going?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: That's you opening a secret stone door. Alright, so there's a locked door to the east and a door to the south.
Nikhil: Okay, so what happens if I click on the lockpick?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you have to try to unlock it. So that's where you would have to roll a skill check. Sleight of hands.
Nikhil: Oh, damn.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow, okay.
Nikhil: okay so my question was like you said the door was locked but if i click click it on the map will it open and show me the map
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think so, it shouldn't.
Nikhil: Okay, yes. Okay, thanks. That's cool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, so you open the door. All right.
Nikhil: All right, go ahead. Okay. This has...
Kostadis Roussos: racks of weapons line the walls of this chamber including spears swords crossbows and bolts a dozen dirty red cloaks hang from the hooks by the door um you notice that this the the red brands have ambitious you so roll an insight or roll an insight check Check.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip! Alright, let's also roll for Pip's Insight. Roll for Pip's Insight.
Nikhil: Copy
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right. Pip says, huh, that's a lot of weapons. Somebody's trying to build an army.
Nikhil: Interesting. Okay, that's all. Pick it up guys. Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Um, so you're going to try to pick up all the equipment. All right. How about carrying it all right now with you would be a bit challenging, but I'll assume that if you empty the dungeon, you can come pick it up or you can try to see if there's anything of particular value.
Nikhil: okay is there some okay uh let's let's see what we can what could be useful to us in the back of and Povit.
Kostadis Roussos: um well so there's like here I'll just describe to you here I'll just dump all right
Nikhil: Redbrand Exo, Pulse Biasic, Shrug Shrug Shrug
Kostadis Roussos: If you're going to pick up a weapon, you can pick up a weapon. Pip is going to pick up a crossbow.
Nikhil: Oh, I like the short sword. I'm gonna swap it with the short sword I have.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Nikhil: It has like semi-pressure stones.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you want a prettier short start. Okay.
Nikhil: See, isn't that the point of like, you know,
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, like, you know, I think that's cool. Yes, I think that's very tasty.
Nikhil: Heroes on the short sword, you know? Weapon acquired.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay. Pip says, well, if you're going to get something pretty, he drops the crossbow that didn't have the semi-precious stones and picks up one that has the semi-precious stones. Sister Mele rolls her eyes. Okay. There's a door to the south.
Kostadis Roussos: Zenvon, are you going to do the investigation thing again?
Nikhil: Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Fifteen. Fifteen.
Nikhil: Was this door locked or open?
Kostadis Roussos: It was unlocked. You haven't opened it yet. Alright, you hear nothing.
Nikhil: I wouldn't worry much because we are all cloaked and disguised, so I'll open them.
Kostadis Roussos: Can I open the door?
Nikhil: Peace.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Three large stone sarcophagi stand with this desolate crypt. Okay, step inside.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching!
Kostadis Roussos: And six skeletons in rusty mail are propped against the walls as if guarding the place. False columns along the walls are carved in the image of spreading oak trees. The double door in the southeast corner is sheathed in tarnished plates.
Nikhil: So fast.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, this just got dark so fast that it escalated quickly.
Kostadis Roussos: What do you mean? Well, they're not moving, so these are like these six skeletons, and they're not currently doing anything.
Nikhil: No, no, no. What I felt was as soon as I opened the door, I saw those three ghost-like people and I was scared. But I'm glad that they're not moving.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Okay.
Nikhil: It actually sent shivers down my spine.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, good. Good, good, good, good, good. I'm glad to hear that.
Nikhil: Okay, okay, ah, interesting, I didn't expect this.
Kostadis Roussos: Um, Sister Mela, uh, comes over there and she rolls her religion, her arcana check. Uh, what is it? Religion? Okay, I'm gonna give her an arcana. Ugh, she detects nothing. Veyra also rolls an arcana check and says, I think they're animated skeletons.
Nikhil: Animated? What do you mean?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, if we walk in there or do something, they might suddenly attack us, so we just better be careful.
Nikhil: Oh f**k, okay, I don't even know where to go next. Where do I go from here? It's a tricky thing to do, it's a tricky task to do.
Kostadis Roussos: So where do you want to go? There's the three sarcophaguses, the door to the north and the door to the south, the door to the northeast and the door to the southeast, and we will stop after your next action.
Nikhil: You just said that if I make a move, if I move forward, these skeletons...
Kostadis Roussos: Oh no, she goes, I don't know. She says, well, they might. I mean, usually when the skeletons are here to attack you right on sight, but these ones haven't moved, so I don't know.
Nikhil: Okay, I'm scared. Is there a scare roll? Did I roll a scare or something?
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, Boss, do you want me to go in front?
Nikhil: I don't want to appear scared.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: What's a history roll? Like, can I get to know the history of something or something?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll, yeah, use your history, roll a history check. What'd you roll?
Nikhil: Alright, that's about 18.
Kostadis Roussos: oh no you rolled fantastic um this used to be the elders this used to be the set the the the where the elders uh what is it a Tresandar Crypts Tresandar Crypts this is where the the old family the elders of the family used to be buried here
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, what are we going to do?
Nikhil: That's relieving to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, there's one more.
Nikhil: One door to the northeast and two doors to the south.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: So, I'm going to open the door in the northeast.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the minute you step over here, the skeletons animate, we roll for initiative, and we stop.
Nikhil: Shit. Oh no.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, that's glad. Oh, fuck. Okay. I'm rolling.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, that's that all done. Let's get on with it.
Nikhil: Thank you for watching.
Kostadis Roussos: Um, Melee goes, oh, these are undead! Um, undead are a kind of monster in Dungeons & Dragons that has, um...
Nikhil: White Walkers
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you wanna, they, uh, yeah, you can say that. Alright, uh, okay, and so we need Sister Maela. She's got a 15.
Nikhil: Can you not quickly run through the door, back to the door?
Kostadis Roussos: Many things can happen, but we're going to stop here.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: You didn't have to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't have to do many things.
Nikhil: I would say this is probably the best part of all the games played so far.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, I mean like of all the sessions that we've played, this is the best cliffhanger or, you know, the best...
Kostadis Roussos: Cliffhanger
Nikhil: Wraithhanger or The Story Progression
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, you know, this is the story, the state, you know, stories have to, it takes a little bit of time for stories to move. Okay, so turn. Okay, we will stop here for and we'll stop here because it's almost nine o'clock. All right.
Nikhil: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Great. It was great hanging with you. It's great hanging with you, man.
Nikhil: Thank you Mike because I missed playing with you last week.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: This was compensated for the last two weeks, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, yes it did. Alright man, take care, have a good one.
Nikhil: See you. Bye-bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye-bye.